

Iraq, Baghdad, Hey Al-Qadisiyah



+9647714848295



noorscastln@gmail.com



LinkedIn Profile



Noor Ali

Bilingual and experienced in customer service, administration, team leading, and secretary. A person with demonstrated history of working in real estate, postal industries and its related managements. Skilled in customer service, management, contractors, Sales and real estate. Strong business development holding a bachelor degree in Language interpretation and translation from Al-Mammoun University Collage.

Experience

Jan 2021- Present

Executive Secretary/ Unicom Group - for Telecommunication Technology

- Coordinating all of the resolutions issued by the superior administration to all other depts.
- Responsible for a secretary team of 2 employees and their daily/weekly/monthly duties.
- Issuing and forming all the formal letters between the company and the governmental sectors.
- Following up with all other depts. (Human resources, logistics, financial, operations, business center, the, and maintenance contracted companies) on daily bases.
- Doing minutes of meetings of the superior administration.
- Attending meetings between the governmental sector and the company's superior administration.
- Following up on any offers received by the company and create contrasts with other offers.
- Arranging meetings, trainings, etc. logistically.

SEP 2020 - Jan 2021

Senior Administrative Coordinator/ Unicom Group - for Telecommunication Technology

- Delegating tasks and ensuring that they are completed in accordance with existing policies and procedures.
- Greeting and directing visitors to the appropriate parties.
- Handling basic office duties, such as answering and routing phones, responding to emails, maintaining employee, financial, and client records, and data entry and reporting.
- Schedule in-house and external meetings.
- Organize dept. documents into updated filing systems
- Answering questions and finding information for employees, vendors, clients, and lenders.
- Supporting employees by facilitating interdepartmental communications and interactions between internal and external parties.
- Ensuring that the office is well-maintained, organized, and secure.
- Developing and implementing new policies and processes.

FEB 2018 -MAY 2020

Customer Service Experience Manager/ Momentum group/Al- Warqaa Real Estate in Turkey/ Iraq

- Helping to develop and implement a customer service policy for an entire organization.
- Finding ways to measure customer satisfaction and improve services.
- Leading or supervising a team of customer service staff 5+ employees.
- Handling face-to-face inquiries from customers.
- Communicating courteously with customers by telephone, email, letter and face to face.
- Investigating and solving customers' problems, which may be complex or long standing problems that have

- been passed on by customer service employees.
- Handling customer complaints or any major incidents rounded around customer service department.
- Issuing refunds or compensation to customers.
- Keeping accurate records of discussions or correspondence with customers.
- Writing reports analysis.
- Developing feedback or complaints procedures for customers to use.
- Improving customer service procedures, policies and standards for your organization or department.
- Meeting with other managers to discuss possible improvements to customer service.
- Being involved in customer service staff recruitment and appraisals.
- Training staff to deliver a high standard of customer service.
- Supporting if needed/possible the Aftersales department to handle any abnormal customers that demands what's behind the line of customer service department.

JUN 2017 -FEB 2018

Office Manager/Forex

- Organizing meetings and managing databases.
- Booking transport and accommodation.
- Organizing company events or conferences.
- Ordering stationery and furniture.
- Dealing with correspondence, complaints and queries.
- Preparing letters, presentations and reports.
- Supervising and monitoring the work of administrative staff.
- Managing office budgets.
- Liaising with staff, suppliers and clients.
- Implementing and maintaining procedures/office administrative systems.
- Delegating tasks to junior employees.
- Organizing induction programs for new employees.
- Ensuring that health and safety policies are up to date.
- Using a range of software packages.
- Attending meetings with senior management assisting the organization's HR function by keeping personnel records up to date, arranging interviews and so on.

Education

MAY 2014

Bachelor Translation English-Arabic / Al-Mammoun University Collage

Certificates & Achievements

- Customer Service Workflow and Manual:-

A full overview on how do the workflow should be in customer service section and what are the duties that should be fulfilled and how.

Certificates:-

- Certificates of Recognition from Al-Wargaa Real Estate Marketing and Trading.

Skills

Computer Skills: MS Office: Word, Excel, and PowerPoint | Skype| Trello| Zoom| Online Storage| Gmail| Outlook |TeamViewer |Dropbox.

Soft Skills: Presentation Skills| Public Speaking| Multitasking| Leadership| Teamwork| Punctuality | Time Management| Quality Assurance| Team Building Expertise| Analytical thinking| Accountability| Conflict Resolution| Problem Solving| Critical Thinking| Working under Pressure| Verbal & Written Communication| Working in a multicultural environment.